If I leave
Here she comes.
cat ears in your room
what will you do?
Another adorable companion of mine.
She is so sublime.
But I like that part of her.
Where is she going?
Ah that.
She has such a wide interest.
No way, that's lewd!
She didn't like those?
So she is into those.
They look good too.
5 minutes pass...
Don't be shy, do as you please.
Just for a little bit...
So she like that.
She looks good in it.
Meow!
She is so cute.
What am I doing?
Ah, a tail.
3 minutes pass...
She has good taste.
I could watch her forever.
Since I have the ears, might as well add the tail.
Yeah if you can put it in your...
This is...
How do I put this on?
N-No way.
I-I don't understand...
I'm sure she understands just fine.
No, no...
No?
Could it be...
Yes yes.
This is to see whether I am wrong.
I'm definitely not interested.
So I just have to put it in, right?
She's finally doing it?
There, right in there.
A bit more.
Almost there.
I came!
I still have a long way to go.
It's only one.
I have to put it all in.
Decided in 0.1 seconds
If I just grab it with my hand like this...
Deeper.
It went it!
This is good.
Just like that.
It goes in and out.
It's in!
Nice.
The big one's left to go in.
How about this?
Is she going to...
Come on, come on...
Can she? Can she?
It's all in!
She was great.